Dad, nothing is happening.
Do you know why I wanted to see you?
Yes, of course.
but sir
the situation is very simple.
With all due respect,
only one person must accept fate.
Didn't Jun Mo start all this?
Eleven years ago
you told me and Lee Choo Woon
that we can all coexist
only if we have a rule.
Yes, he said.
And Jun Mo was the one who broke this rule.
I'm not talking about a rule.
I am about coexistence.
This is frustrating. It's like I'm talking to a wall.
If you want coexistence,
had to follow the rules.
If Jun Mo dies, so will coexistence.
I spoke with Lee Choo Woon,
he understood everything.
And Chuvun will not get involved.
Really?
Money really can do a lot, right?
I thought Gi Seok cared about him.
Only one problem remains.
Nam Gi Joon.
He will die - that's the end.
but sir
you know no worse than me
he just doesn't give up.
That's why I need your help.
You desire coexistence more than anyone else.
At any cost. But do it.
If you don't want to see another one
bloody slaughter, like 11 years ago.
Like father, like son.
WITHOUT MERCY
Hang on.
I will come for you.
"Hang on"? To hell with it.
You know, like a confrontation before a fight.
Are we expecting someone?
Were there any orders?
Probably a couple
looking for a place to stay Send them away.
This place is not for them.
Civilians cannot come here. drive through
What?
Devil.
In my opinion, you are civilians.
Gu inside?
What the hell?
Cattle!
Everyone ahead!
Well, because!
What?
You want me to fight
with some gang?
What are you, fat man
do you really not know who I am?
I'm Jung In Seok, the champion.
I am aware.
You were caught on doping,
and you lost your title.
Didn't I say?
Repeat it again - you are a corpse.
Didn't I say that?
This fight is worth a billion.
listen
I can kill him by accident.
That's great.
Fools! There were many of you here!
And you let him escape?
Jung In Suk I know?
Answer, damn it.
Yes, sir. It's him.
Chon Agency.
You have to call them first.
And look for Mr. Gu.
Hotels, clubs, saunas, country establishments,
even the most unexpected places. Clear?
Why are you still here?
Ahead.
sir
where are you now
Nam Gi Joon is still alive.
What?
So I ran away to kill him.
Where can it be found?
Things change, huh?
Once you endured and not like this,
despite numerous injuries.
I know
I heard what happened to Gi Seok.
no matter what i say
you're still going to hunt down the culprit, right?
Well, I won't bother you.
But first I'll patch you up. Then take revenge.
It's not too late yet.
TEGVAN CLINIC
Hey brother, are you holding on?
don't let go
Greetings.
I have a meeting with Choo Woon tomorrow.
I'll tell him to follow the rules
in connection with the death of Gi Seok.
I told you not to do anything.
Gi June.
promise me
Gi Seok would like that.
Who the hell are you?
I will call back.
who do you think you are
what are you discussing, how to punish me?
GI JUN
Is this Nam Gi Joon? Let him go here.
The one he's looking for is here.
So you are Gu Bong San's son.
You are kind of rude.
They say you're the same
like your old man in his youth
but I don't see it.
Many people want you dead, not just me.
Do yourself a favor, disappear.
Don't you want to live a little longer?
Did I at least once...
asked to spare my life?
What the hell is this scumbag
and everyone sneaks around so much?
Mr. Gu!
Sir!
Stop it! Come on!
What the hell?
Stop it! Mr. Gu.
Enough already!
I'm sorry
but you must stop.
Agov, Pyong Go.
Somehow you ended up here quickly.
Amazing, Kim. You are usually late.
Ahoy!
Let me ask something.
Were you in such a hurry because you were worried about me?
were you worried
for him or for Nam Gi Joon?
say
Hatching!
- Cattle!
- Let go.
I told you to stop!
It was necessary not to get into anything, carrion!
- Let go!
- Do you want to know?
Then I'll tell you, scoundrel.
All because you
worthless creature, you ruined everything!
Gi Seok and Pyeong Go…'
You killed them, you fucking asshole.
let go
Dovban is a loser.
Are you finally honest?
Damn scum.
Stop!
As they say
traitor is forever, right?
Ahoy!
But you are wrong about something.
Is this guy?
He died because of you.
You're an asshole. You are to blame for everything.
Because you couldn't
get rid of Nam Gi Joon. Clear?
Did you get it or not?
Scoundrel!
Enough, fuck it.
Enough?
If you have already started, do it properly.
Let's go from here.
Come on.
GI JUN
Pyeong Go, I understand you...'
Mr. Nam Gi Joon.
About your friends…
They are all dead because of you.
Because if he has already started,
everything must be done properly.
I will send the address. Come here.
Can you run?
Sim Song Won, it's me.
Who the hell are you? I'm from the police!
Yes, I know.
You are from the police.
Mr. Gu.
You've been here before, right?
Thanks to you, me too
came back here after so many years.
If you don't want to end your life,
like all who died here
start talking
Mr. Chairman.
Why do you do this?
I read the report on the murder
Nam Gi Seok. He is very interesting.
You arrived first
to the crime scene, right?
I doubt that with such service
go on night patrols.
And there was no challenge either.
So you knew, right?
You knew Nam Gi Seok was going to die.
That's bullshit.
- Call the boys.
- Of course.
Yes, this is the perfect place.
No one will know if someone dies here.
How the hell did he bring us here?
I think we are there. Get ready
what are you eating
Ahoy! The door is locked.
Come here already.
What is it?
You look at his peak. Scary as hell.
- What?
- Who are you?
- Do you want to kill me?
- How fun.
Let everyone go out.
- What is happening?
- What uncle?
What is this?
Trembling
It seems that money takes its toll.
How many authoritative people are here.
What does he drink?
It is an honor for me.
What does he want to say?
As some of you already know,
I will take over soon
by Bonsan Corporation.
And when that happens,
I plan to replace the entire staff
to new people.
That is, on my people.
And for the security company
i can expand the business.
Anyway,
it will be something of a test.
Are you worthy of Bonsan in the future?
The task is simple.
A man will come here soon. And you must
bring him to me
- What is it?
- What the hell?
Go take a look.
What is it?
This is cash.
- Is it money?
- Ah!
- Bundles of cash?
- Hell, to hell with it.
I agree!
That's it.
He will tell us everything.
Who will bring him to me
he will receive a bag.
Do whatever you want with it.
But don't kill him.
I will do it myself.
Are you kidding me?
So much money for him alone?
Aww, don't be so serious.
have fun This is such a game.
Hey, kid. Are you alone here?
What the hell?
So that you don't regret later...
better go away
Seriously? What does he drink?
- From the road.
- Steel eggs.
- Don't push!
- Out of the way! Away!
Cattle!
What are you waiting for?
Whore you are!
Shit!
Don't come, you bastard!
Hey, carrion!
Come on, bastard!
Devil.
Protection.
- Sir
- Don't bring him, but kill him.
Just kill him!
let's go Shout out!
You son of a bitch!
Ahoy!
Beat him!
Blyaha, back!
Agov.
What, scared?
Can you kill him?
You know what I can do.
Ha?
But I think we need to discuss the amount again.
- Double it.
- Are you kidding me?
Am I kidding?
Does it look like I'm kidding?
I recorded…
the entire phone call.
You can listen.
Teenagers who killed
Nam Gi-seok, surrender.
But make sure
so that there are no traces of other people
"Other people"?
You know, kill that bastard.
Devil!
Stupid bastard!
Badge.
Agov.
Double the amount. Two billion.
If you have doubts, you can try it yourself.
Well you
So what? Already changed your mind?
Oh, you scumbag...
A lot of shit.
Aww, Mr. Nam Gi Joon.
I'm waiting here.
Infection.
Devil.
That's shit.
Agov. I will really kill him.
Go ahead.
This is…
Shit bastard.
Aww, Nam Gi Joon.
Is that your brother, Nam Gi Seok?
Yes, I killed him.
Miserable loser.
Devil! My eye!
Damn it!
A stupid coward.
Yes.
Ahoy!
Shaking!
Where the hell are you? Shaking!
don't come near me
Ah, son of a bitch!
Mr. Nam Gi Joon.
Let's stop here.
stop, okay?
Don't kill me!
Curse!
Bullshit
Agov.
What is the difference to you?
It won't bring your brother back!
Pick up the phone.
This subscriber is currently unavailable...
Ah, Jun Mo. are you well
Do you hear me, are you okay?
Say something.
It's me.
Why Jun Mo…
Gi Jun, listen to me first.
It wasn't Jun Mo who did it.
With Gu Jun Mo
I acted according to the rule.
What…
what are you saying
Your son
dead.
No.
Give me Jun Mo.
Immediately!
Put up with it.
Listen, Nam Gi Joon.
Curse! You son of a bitch!
Jun Mo…
No, it is impossible.
My son could not die.
No.
I've always been interested.
When you went to the head O instead of me,
I was wondering how you were feeling.
But now...
I don't even have to ask.
And about the jacket.
I will give it next time.
We will meet again.
Nam Gi Joon…
he was taken care of.
WITHOUT MERCY
Translation of subtitles: Olga Tsiatska